

I am passionate about coding for over 10+ years of my working experience and participating in the software development which includes technical design, coding, CI/CD, integration test and support of production issues.

I enjoy to learn new programming languages to grow and enhance my technical abilities.

SUPAKORN SRABOUR

PHONE:

+66 61 542 8288

EMAIL:

Peat2009@hotmail.com

ADDRESS:

98/11 Moo.4 Bangmaenang, Bangyai, Nonthaburi 11140

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science (Software Engineering) GPA 3.6

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok (2014)

Bachelor of Science (Electronic Business) GPA 3.22

Prince of Songkla University (2011)

SKILLS

Programming:

<u>Backend</u>: Java, JSP, JSF, Spring Boot, EJB, Hibernate, Servlet, RESTful WS, SQL, XML, JSON

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

React JS

Database: MySQL, Oracle, DB2,

MongoDB

Control Source: CVS, SVN, GitHub,

GitLab

Server: JBoss, GlassFish, Tomcat,

WebLogic

Tools: Eclipse, NetBeans, SQL Developer, Jenkins, Jfrog, Docker, OpenShift

WORK EXPERIENCES

Advanced Software Engineer | Kasikorn Business-Technology Group (KBTG)

Oct 2020 - Present

- Coding and create interactive UI with React JS
- Design and coding backend API with Spring Boot
- Guide and review code for junior developer
- Apply CI/CD pipeline for DevSecOps
- Support, investigate and solve production issues

IT Specialist | MIMO Tech Company Limited (Subsidiary of AIS Public Company Limited)

Mar 2019 - Sep 2020

- Gathering requirement from customers
- Estimate the impact of business change
- Analyze business model to design database
- Design and coding backend API with Spring and Hibernate
- Guide and review code for junior-senior developer
- Support, investigate and solve production issues

Senior Programmer Analyst | MIMO Tech Company Limited (Subsidiary of AIS Public Company Limited)

Mar 2015 - Feb 2019

- Design database
- Coding web application with JSF, Spring and Hibernate
- Code review for develop team
- Investigate and solve production issues

Software Engineer | Gosoft (Thailand) Company Limited (Subsidiary of CP ALL Public Company Limited)

Mar 2014 - Feb 2015

- Gathering requirement from customers
- Analyze and design system flow and work processes
- Coding with Java in Agile software development
- Debugging and maintaining System

Programmer | Samart Corporation Public Company

Oct 2013 - Feb 2014

- Coding web application with Javascript
- Debugging and maintaining software

Software Engineer | The Ultimate Soft Company Limited

Apr 2011 - Sep 2013

- Design database
- Coding web application with JSP, JSF and EJB
- Debugging and maintaining system

PROJECT HANDLE

- Wealth PLUS on K+ Application
- Digital Trading System (Support for AIS Shop, Telewiz and Partner)
- Trading Management System (Support for AIS Shop, Telewiz and Partner)
- Retail Master Ordering System (Support for 7-Eleven)
- Web Analytics Report for LawDD Website
- NxAdmin for LawDD Website
- NxDM Virtual Library
 - Administrator Management for Chulalongkorn University